Subscribe
to the BankBazaar.com channel and press the bell button to
watch the video first. Hello friends,
welcome to our YouTube channel
BankBazaar.com. Friends, if you are interested in
removing the lid of your account, then
watch this video carefully. In this video,
we will tell you
important information related to that bank account. Today, we will
tell you how you can generate that bank account statement.
Friends, for this you will have to
log in to the mobile application. If
you have not yet logged in to your mobile,
then we have given the link in the description box.
You can activate this application from there and
login.
Now see, we have entered the login ID here
and opened our mobile application.
You will see that the
statement option is coming here. By clicking on it,
we have to go to the detail statement.
After opening the detail statement, you will see that here you have the option of last month,
three months, six months, building near.
And if you want a statement of financial year or
any political date, then
you
can generate the statement by clicking on the start from the end below and selecting your date. Here we have  If we want to
take out the statement from 1st April 2019 to 1st April 2030, then we will enter this date
here and click on the profit button. As
soon as we make a profit, we will see that
our next button will open where
you will see the view PDF option and next to it
you will see this and over email ID. So
first of all, if you want to take it in PDF, then
you will use it and download it from here. You will
see at the top, you
will go to this three white line and here the download
option is coming. By going here you will download your file
and you will see that our file has been downloaded.
Here you are seeing the download computer
and if you want to send it on mail, then
here the send mail option is coming,
here you will enter your email ID
which is already visible here
and you will send it on that, then
your financial year statement has been
sent to the mail ID successfully. So
friends, in this way you
can download your account statement. So friends,
if you liked this video, then like this
video and subscribe to this channel.  Do it
and press the bell icon
so that you keep getting notifications of our every upcoming video.
Thank you
friends.